canopy.co 2014-06-25

# Privacy - Canopy

##  Privacy Policy 

Last updated on May 21, 2014 

#### Policy purpose

Canopy App (“Canopy”) provides this Privacy Policy to inform you of our policies and procedures for the collection, use and disclosure of personal information we receive from users of [canopy.co](http://canopy.co/) (this “Site”). This Privacy Policy only applies to information you provide to us through the Site. 

This Privacy Policy may change from time to time. We will not reduce your rights under this Privacy Policy without your consent. We will post all privacy policy changes on this page canopy.co/privacy. If changes are significant, we will provide a more prominent notice (including, for certain services, email notification of privacy policy changes). 

#### Information we collect

We will create your Account based upon the Personal Information you provide, and you will become a Member of Canopy. Your Personal Information will be used to provide our service. Canopy collects and stores all information provided by its visitors and members. This includes, but is not limited to: registration information, profile activity, IP addresses, referral pages, service behavior, and traffic data. We will not log your information or behavior on other third party applications unrelated to Canopy. 

All Members may review, update, correct or delete Personal Information in their Account by editing such profile via the Site. If you completely delete all such information, then your Account may become deactivated. We will make efforts to honor your request. We may retain an archived copy of your records as required by law or for legitimate business purposes. 

#### Your data

Your data serves the following functions: 

  1. Allows Canopy to better understand Site usage and subsequently improve content, functionality, and features of the Site. 
  2. Information you provide to Canopy may be used for Customer Service, Accounting, and New Product Promotion. Canopy may use aggregate or anonymous information which will not be linked to identified individuals for various other uses for itself and third parties. 

#### Third parties

We will not share your personal information with any third parties for direct marketing purposes. We will only disclose personal information to third parties if we are required to by applicable laws, regulations, or legal and regulatory processes, or if there is a sale, merger, transfer, or exchange of control of Canopy to another company. 

We may share consolidated non-personally-identifiable data that does not include Personal Information and we may otherwise disclose Log Data with third parties for industry analysis, demographic profiling and other purposes. Any aggregated information shared in these contexts will not contain your specific Personal Information. 

By request, individuals may review their Personal Information or logged site behavior contained in Canopy files by contacting the Canopy Privacy Officer. All requests for this data will be provided within a 30 day period. If an individual believes any of their personal information is inaccurate, we will make appropriate corrections. 

Canopy may also provide your Personal Information to our consultants, subcontractors, and professional advisers (which shall be bound by privacy obligations) to assist our uses disclosed herein. We use subcontractors located in United States of America and Canada to process personal information for Data Backup and Customer Record Keeping, therefore your information may be transferred to and stored on computers located outside of your province, state, or country. Your consent to this Privacy Policy followed by your submission of such information represents your agreement to that transfer. More information can be obtained from our Privacy Officer. 

#### External links

Our Site contains links to Amazon. If you choose to purchase a product by "clicking on" a product on Canopy you will be directed to Amazon’s website. We do not take responsibility for cookies or other files that could be placed on your computer by Amazon. We encourage you to read [Amazon's privacy policy](http://www.amazon.com/gp/help/customer/display.html?nodeId=468496) if you have concerns with their behavior. 

#### Membership

When you register as a member of Canopy, you are agreeing to receive emails and in-system notices for announcements, newsletters, recommendations and policy updates. If you would like to opt out of our emails, please contact the privacy officer at privacy@canopy.co, or follow up unsubscribe link on those emails. 

Canopy reserves the right to delete your account without notice, for legitimate business reasons. In the unlikely even that this occurs, we will provide an email notification with further details. 

#### Membership termination

If you would like your public profile and membership with Canopy terminated, log in, go to your profile and click the "Edit" button. Then follow the "Delete my account" link. 

#### The Public and the Community

Non members (the “Public”) and members of Canopy will be able to view your public profile, including: your first name, surname, Canopy username, personal website, users you follow, followers, recommended items, and number of items recommended. 

If you have any questions about this Policy or any of the context described, please contact us at: 

**Canopy Team  
** c/o Michael Feldstein  
1715 McAllister St. Suite 202  
San Francisco CA 94115 

or send us an email at [privacy@canopy.co](mailto:privacy@canopy.co).
